&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们将进入我认为是皇冠上的宝石
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We're going to move
into what I think is the crown jewel
我们今天谈论的很多东西。
of a lot of stuff we've
been talking about today.
首先想象一下JavaScript性能和网络性能。
Imagine first the JavaScript performance
and the network performance.
如果我说，你可以用一个诡异的把戏戏剧性地修复两者，对吗？
If I said, you can fix both dramatically
with one weird trick, right?
你会点击那个链接诱饵文章，你完全会的，对吧？
You'd click that link bait article,
you totally would, right?
所以我们来谈谈这个，
So let's talk about that,
这是惰性加载和预加载与反应和webpack。
which is lazy-loading and
pre-loading with React and webpack.
我们知道Javascript是要付出代价的，对吧？
We know that there's a cost to Javascript,
right?
我们知道网络是有成本的，对吧？
We know that there is a cost
to the network, right?
如果我们能减少一点那就太酷了。
It'd be cool if we could
reduce that a little bit.
首先，为了表明我的观点，我要出去
First, just to kinda make my
point I'm gonna go out for
又是两条金科玉律。
the two golden rules again.
不做事比做事快。
Not doing stuff is
faster than doing stuff.
这是我认为第一个的改写版本。
This is I think a reworded
version of the first one.
以后再做事情是现在不做的一种方式，因此更快，对吧？
Doing stuff later is a way to not do
it now, and is thereby faster, right?
因为这是现在不做的一个版本。
Cuz it's a version of not doing it now.
所以有一条来自Sean Larkin的推文，他在Webpack团队工作。
So there's a tweet from Sean Larkin
who works in the Webpack team.
这有点像设定了一个捆绑包的目标，所有的捆绑包，
It's kind of setting a goal of bundles,
all bundles,
所有JavaScript小于300KB。
all JavaScript being
less than 300 kilobytes.
你就像，但是你给我看了一个图表，而且这个图表很大，[笑]对吗？
You're like, but you showed me a graph,
and the graph is big, [LAUGH] right?
我的应用程序在完全加载时是我认为
My application when
fully loaded is I think
就像5兆字节的东西，贯穿整个过程。
like five megabytes of stuff,
the whole way through.
但请注意，这里有一个词是懒惰的或者不是。
But notice there,
there's a word kind of lazily or not.
如果你不是一下子就需要所有的东西呢。
What if you don't need
everything all at once.
所以，我认为我正在开发的应用程序是Ingrid，对吗？
So, I think about the app I
working on is InGrid, right?
有一个完整的编辑器用于操作活动，还有一个代码编辑器和
There's a full editor for manipulating
campaigns, and there's a code editor and
所有这些疯狂的事情。
there's all of these crazy things.
有一种东西可以上传你的联系人和
There's a thing for
uploading your contacts and
一堆不同的特征。
a bunch of different features.
我不知道那个人来那里做什么，所以我把所有的东西都寄给他们了，对吧？
I don't know what the person came there
to do, so I send them everything, right?
他们可能不需要整个DragonDrop编辑器
They might not need that
entire DragonDrop editor and
WizzyWig文本编辑器喜欢唤醒和风格之类的东西。
the WizzyWig text editor like wake and
style stuff.
如果使用代码编辑器，则可能不需要代码编辑器。
They might not need the code
editor if they're using that.
如果他们只是上传一些新的上下文，他们可能不需要这两个。
They might not need either of those if
they're just uploading some new context.
如果他们只是去调整一些设置或者
They might not need even that if they are
just going and tweaking some settings or
处理我们发送给他们的一些警报，或者
dealing with some alert that we sent them,
or
检查他们最近竞选活动的统计数据，对吧？
checking on the stats of their
most recent campaign, right?
但现在
But right now, and
我正在努力解决这个问题，但现在，我们把所有东西都寄给他们了，对吧？
I'm working on fixing this, but right now,
we send them absolutely everything, right?
他们收到所有这些代码，他们必须将这些代码打包。
And they receive all this code,
they have to parcel this code.
就像他们付出了那样的代价，
Like they pay that cost,
这是一个巨大的黄色鼻涕虫，我在我们应用程序的屏幕截图中向您展示了它。
that's a giant yellow slug that I showed
you on the screen shot of our application.
公平地说，这是我们在该页面上的拖放编辑器。
In fairness that is our drag and
drop editor on that page.
但考虑到我说了同样的话无论如何，
But considering I said in
the same bundle no matter what,
他们不管怎样都要付出这个代价。
they're paying that cost regardless.
所以如果我能给他们发送更少的代码，他们必须喜欢，
So if I can send them less code,
they have to like,
更少的代码必须通过管道。
less code has to go through the tube.
在管道的另一边出现的代码更少，这意味着他们必须
Less code shows up at the other side
of the tube which means they have to
少解析代码，好吗？
parse less code, all right?
如果他们解析更少的代码，那会更快，因为我们看到的所有疯狂的东西
If they parse less code, that's gonna be
faster, cuz all the crazy stuff we saw
早些时候，不这样做比做要快，对吧？
earlier, not doing that is
faster than doing it, right?
然后我们可以给他们看
And then we can show them,
然后，如果他们想去编辑，我会把代码发给他们，对吗？
then if they want to go to the editor,
I'll send them that code later, right?
我不会给他们发送模型空间代码编辑器，上下文上传的东西。
And I won't send them the model space
code editor, the context uploading thing.
因为他们需要东西，我会寄给他们比他们多一点的东西
As they need stuff,
I will send them small bits more that they
实际上需要在他们通过申请时，对吗？
actually need as they go
through the application, right?
因为以后做是现在不做的一种方式，现在不做更快。
Cuz doing it later is a way to not do
it now, and not doing it now is faster.